<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="ScreenViewer.xsl"?>
<!-- 
LICENSE NOTE:

Copyright  2003-2007 Active Agenda Inc., All Rights Reserved.

Unless explicitly acquired and licensed from Licensor under a "commercial license",
the contents of this file are subject to the Reciprocal Public License ("RPL")
Version 1.4, or subsequent versions as allowed by the RPL,and You may not copy
or use this file in either source code or executable form, except in compliance
with the terms and conditions of the RPL. You may obtain a copy of the RPL from
Active Agenda Inc. at http://www.activeagenda.net/license.

All software distributed under the Licenses is provided strictly on an "AS IS"
basis, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AND ACTIVE AGENDA
INC. HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL SUCH WARRANTIES, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY 
WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, QUIET ENJOYMENT,
OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. See the Licenses for specific language governing rights and
limitations under the Licenses.

author         Dan Zahlis <dzahlis@activeagenda.net>
author         Mattias Thorslund <mthorslund@activeagenda.net>
copyright      2003-2007 Active Agenda Inc.
license        http://www.activeagenda.net/license
-->
<Module name="Code Items" moduleID="cod" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="ModuleDef.xsd" updateImports="yes" dataCollectionForm="yes" isMasterData="yes" singularRecordName="Code Item" pluralRecordName="Code Items">
    <ModuleFields>
        <TableField name="CodeID" type="int" dbFlags="not null" phrase="Code ID|A number used to track code records" sample="1"/>
        <TableField name="CodeTypeID" type="int" dbFlags="not null" phrase="Code Type ID|A number used to track code records" sample="1"/>
        <TableField name="SortOrder" type="int" phrase="Sort Order|A numerical value to define the placement of this code in an ordered list, such as drop-down list." sample="100"/>
        <TableField name="Value" type="varchar(25)" phrase="Value|This field has special meaning for different code types. It can be used to limit a list of codes based on a matching value." sample="10"/>
        <TableField name="Description" type="varchar(128)" phrase="Description|The text that should be displayed for this code. This is the standard-language text (English). Additional languages are supported by adding columns using the standard language ID as the name." sample="Supplier"/>
        <ForeignField name="CodeTypeTitle" foreignTable="codt" foreignKey="CodeTypeID" foreignField="Name" key="CodeTypeID" joinType="left" phrase="Code Type|The name of the present code type." sample="Organization Category"/>
        <ForeignField name="CodeTypeDescription" foreignTable="codt" foreignKey="CodeTypeID" foreignField="Description" key="CodeTypeID" joinType="left" phrase="Description|A clarifying descrition of the code type" sample="A system for classifying types of potential loss"/>
        <CombinedField name="RecordLabel" phrase="Record Label|The short, concise, label of the record for display purposes" sample="Mattias Thorslund | 01-01-2006 | Ongoing"><CombinedFieldRef name="CodeTypeTitle"/>;_<CombinedFieldRef name="Description"/></CombinedField>
        <CombinedField name="Code" phrase="Code|A combined field used to describer the record when associating it with other records" sample="Mattias Thorslund | 01-01-2006 | Ongoing"><CombinedFieldRef name="CodeTypeTitle"/>;_<CombinedFieldRef name="Description"/></CombinedField>
    </ModuleFields>
    <ModuleInfo>
        <PrimaryKey>
            <FieldRef name="CodeTypeID"/>
            <FieldRef name="CodeID"/>
        </PrimaryKey>
        <!--<OwnerField name="OrganizationID"/>-->
        <!--<RecordDescriptionField name="Code"/> REMOVED - MJT 02/09/06. This functionality will not work due to more than one PK-->
        <RecordLabelField name="RecordLabel"/>
    </ModuleInfo>
    <Screens>
        <ListScreen name="List" phrase="List|List codes">
            <ListField name="CodeTypeID" phrase="Code Type ID"/>
            <ListField name="CodeTypeTitle" phrase="Code Type"/>
            <ListField name="CodeID" phrase="Code ID"/>
            <ListField name="Description" phrase="Description"/>
            <ListField name="SortOrder" phrase="Sort Order"/>
            <ListField name="Value" phrase="Value"/>
        </ListScreen>
        <ViewScreen name="CodeView" phrase="View|View codes">
            <ViewField name="CodeTypeID"/>
            <ViewField name="CodeTypeTitle"/>
            <ViewField name="CodeID"/>
            <ViewField name="Description"/>
            <ViewField name="SortOrder"/>
            <ViewField name="Value"/>
        </ViewScreen>
        <EditScreen name="CodeEdit" phrase="Form|Edit codes">
            <ViewField name="CodeTypeID"/>
            <ViewField name="CodeTypeTitle"/>
            <EditField name="CodeID" size="10" maxLength="10"/>
            <EditField name="Description" size="50" maxLength="128"/>
            <EditField name="SortOrder" size="10" maxLength="10"/>
            <EditField name="Value" size="15" maxLength="25"/>
        </EditScreen>
        <RecordReportScreen name="RecordReports" phrase="Reports|View reports on the current injury/illness"/>
        <ListReportScreen name="ListReports" phrase="Reports|View reports based on active search criteria"/>
    </Screens>
    <Exports>
        <ViewGrid moduleID="cod" phrase="Code Items">
            <ViewField name="CodeID" phrase="CodeID" sample="1"/>
            <InvisibleField name="CodeTypeID" phrase="CodeTypeID"/>
            <ViewField name="Description" phrase="Description" sample="Human Safety"/>
            <ViewField name="SortOrder" phrase="SortOrder" sample="10"/>
            <ViewField name="Value" phrase="Value" sample="1"/>
        </ViewGrid>
        <EditGrid moduleID="cod" phrase="Code Items" name="CodeEdit">
            <EditField name="CodeID" size="10" maxLength="10" phrase="CodeID"/>
            <InvisibleField name="CodeTypeID" phrase="CodeTypeID"/>
            <EditField name="Description" size="50" maxLength="128" phrase="Description"/>
            <EditField name="SortOrder" size="10" maxLength="10" phrase="SortOrder"/>
            <EditField name="Value" size="15" maxLength="25" phrase="Value"/>
        </EditGrid>
    </Exports>
    <Documentation>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="Introduction" title="Introduction">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>The installation-specific introduction to the scope and purpose of this module should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said to introduce this module. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="Implementation" title="Implementation">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific implementation rules, policies, practices should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about implementating this module. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="PeopleElements" title="People Elements">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific information regarding the way this module impacts people should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about how this module impacts, or is impacted by, people in general. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="BarrierstoSuccess" title="Barriers to success">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific barriers to success in implemeting this module should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about barriers to success associated with the subject matter of this module.  You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="DataCollection" title="Data Collection">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific data collection methods, locations, and resources should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about collecting the types of data associated with the subject matter of this module. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="DataInput" title="Data Input">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific data input methods, permissions, and requirements should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about inputting the types of data associated with the subject matter of this module. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="OrganizationalInfo" title="Organizational Information">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific knowledge and information that impacts the subject matter of this module should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about organizational considerations associated with the subject matter of this module. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="CommonPractices" title="Common Practices and Alternatives">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific knowledge of common or past practices should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about common practices associated with the subject matter of this module and opportunities for change enabled by the Active Agenda project. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="OrganizationalLearning" title="Organizational Learning">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific learning goals, purposes, and opportunities should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about organizational learning associated with the subject matter of this module.  You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="Training" title="Training">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific training considerations and requirements should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about training associated with the subject matter of this module.  You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="ApplyKnowledge" title="Applying Knowledge">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific knowledge application methods should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see what the active agenda community has said about applying the knowledge collected in association with the subject matter of this module.  You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
        <DocumentationSection sectionID="FAQ" title="Frequently Asked Questions">
            <p>
                <b>"Your Text Here"</b>
            </p>
            <p>Installation-specific questions that are frequently asked of administrators or implementers should be entered here. You can click the online documentation link beneath the table of contents to see the types of questions collected, and answers provided, by the Active Agenda community relating to the subject matter of this module. You are welcome to collect the thoughts of the community, copy them into your local documentation, and extend them to satisfy your local needs.</p>
        </DocumentationSection>
    </Documentation>
    <Revision author="$Author: dan $" id="$Revision: 503 $" date="$Date: 2007-02-17 04:46:15 -0800 (Sat, 17 Feb 2007) $"/>
</Module>
